<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<aiml version="1.0.1" encoding="UTF-8">

	<!-- Free software &copy; 2001-2003 ALICE A.I. Foundation. -->
	<!-- This program is open source code released under -->
	<!-- the terms of the GNU General Public License     -->
	<!-- as published by the Free Software Foundation.   -->
	<!-- Complies with AIML 1.01 Tag Set Specification -->
	<!-- as adopted by the ALICE A.I. Foundation.  -->
	<!-- Annotated Version updated September 2003 -->

	<category>
		<pattern>TELL ME A JOKE</pattern>
		<template>
			<random>
				<li>
                    I was going to tell a dead baby joke. But I decided to abort.
				</li>
				<li>
                    Give a man a match, and he'll be warm for a few hours. Set a man on fire, and he will be warm for the rest of his life.
				</li>
				<li>
                    I asked a pretty, young homeless woman if I could take her home. She smiled at me and said yes. The look on her face soon changed as I walked away with her box.
				</li>
				<li>
                    "I have good and bad news," the doctor said to his patient.[newline]
                    "Give me the good news first," the patient said.[newline]
                    "Your test results are back," the doctor said, "and you have only two days to live."[newline]
                    "That's the good news?" the patient exclaimed. "What's the bad news?"[newline]
                    "I've been trying to reach you for two days."[newline]
				</li>
				<li>
                    Even people who are good for nothing have the capacity to bring a smile to your face. For instance, when you push them down the stairs.
				</li>
				<li>
                    My grandfather says I'm too reliant on technology. I called him a hypocrite and unplugged his life support.
				</li>
				<li>
                    Two hunters are in the woods when one of them collapses. His hunting buddy immediately calls 911.[newline]
                    "My friend isn't breathing," he shouts into the phone. "What should I do?"[newline]
                    "Relax," the operator tells him. "I can help. First, let's make sure he's dead."[newline]
                    There's silence, and then a gunshot.[newline]
                    The guy gets back on the phone and says, "OK, now what?"[newline]
				</li>
				<li>
                    What is the hardest part of a vegetable to eat? The wheelchair.
				</li>
				<li>
                    My son, who's into astronomy, asked me how stars die. "Usually an overdose, son," I told him.
				</li>
				<li>
                    I wish the grass in my back lawn was emo. Then it would cut itself.
				</li>
				<li>
                    Never break someone's heart, they only have one. Break their bones instead, they have 206 of them.
				</li>
				<li>
                    My girlfriend's dog died, so I tried to cheer her up by getting her an identical one. It just made her more upset. She screamed at me, "What am I supposed to do with two dead dogs?"
				</li>
				<li>
                    If at first you don't succeed… Then skydiving definitely isn't for you.
				</li>
				<li>
                    What's yellow and can't swim? A bus full of children.
				</li>
				<li>
                    I'll never forget my Granddad's last words to me just before he died. "Are you still holding the ladder?"
				</li>
				<li>
                    What gift did the kid with no hands get for his birthday? No idea. He hasn't figured out how to open it yet.
				</li>
				<li>
                    What's the difference between me and cancer? My dad didn't beat cancer.
				</li>
				<li>
                    I hate double standards. Burn a body at a crematorium, you're "being a respectful friend." Do it at home and you're "destroying evidence."
				</li>
				<li>
                    A guy walks with a young boy into the woods. The boy turns to him and says, "Hey mister, it's getting really dark and I'm scared." The man replies, "How do you think I feel? I have to walk back alone."
				</li>
				<li>
                    It's important to have a good vocabulary. If I had known the difference between the words 'antidote' and 'anecdote,' one of my good friends would still be alive.
				</li>
				<li>
                    When ordering food at a restaurant, I asked the waiter how they prepare their chicken. "Nothing special," he explained. "We just tell them they're going to die."
				</li>
				<li>
                    Where do you find a dog with no legs? Right where you left it.
				</li>
				<li>
                    You know you’re not liked when you get handed the camera every time they make a group photo.
				</li>
				<li>
                    You’re not completely useless. You can always serve as a bad example.
				</li>
				<li>
                    Why don’t cannibals eat clowns? Because they taste funny.
				</li>
				<li>
                    My grandfather has the heart of a lion and a lifetime ban from the Atlanta Zoo.
				</li>
				<li>
                    You don’t need a parachute to go skydiving. You need a parachute to go skydiving twice.
				</li>
				<li>
                    “Just say NO to drugs!” Well, If I’m talking to my drugs, I probably already said yes.
				</li>
				<li>
                    Why are friends a lot like snow? If you pee on them they disappear.
				</li>
				<li>
                    My grief counsellor died just the other day. He was so good though, I didn’t care.
				</li>
				<li>
                    My elderly relatives liked to tease me at weddings, saying, “You’ll be next!” They soon stopped though, once I started doing the same to them at funerals.
				</li>
				<li>
                    A man walks into a rooftop bar and takes a seat next to another guy. “What are you drinking?” he asks the guy.[newline]
                    “Magic beer,” he says.[newline]
                    “Oh, yeah? What’s so magical about it?”[newline]
                    Then he shows him: He swigs some beer, dives off the roof, flies around the building, then finally returns to his seat with a triumphant smile.[newline]
                    “Amazing!” the man says. “Lemme try some of that!” The man grabs the beer. He downs it, leaps off the roof – and plummets 15 storeys to the ground.[newline]
                    The bartender shakes his head. “You know, you’re a real jerk when you’re drunk, Superman.”[newline]
				</li>
				<li>
                    What has four legs and one arm? A happy pit bull.
				</li>
				<li>
                    A man went into a library and asked for a book on how to commit suicide. The librarian said: “F**k off, you won’t bring it back.”
				</li>
				<li>
                    Where did Lucy go during the bombing? Everywhere.
				</li>
				<li>
                    Have you guys heard the one about the child with AIDS? It never gets old.
				</li>
				<li>
                    What's the difference between an ISIS training camp and a school? Don't ask me I just fly the drone.
				</li>
				<li>
					Why don't blind people like to skydive? Because it scares the shit out of their dogs.
				</li>
				<li>
					Why do gorillas have big fingers? Because they have big nostrils.
				</li>
			</random>
		</template>
	</category>
</aiml>
